Excuse me, sir. Quick question for
you, man. Is this your Lamborghini?
Yeah, it is.
What do you do for a living, man? How are
you able to afford a Lamborghini out in Los Angeles?
Finance. So I'm in private equity.
I went into the entertainment industry. Full on.
I have some of the highest paid people that
have ever made the biggest network deals in reality TV.
I own a law firm in Los Angeles.
What's been the most amount of money
that you've ever generated in a single year?
Multiple millions, yeah.
Oh, over five million.
Well, we're not going to say
that number, but it's in the millions.
Back in 2017 or 18, they told
me they don't even use my figures
because I was doing more
business than anyone in Beverly Hills.
I have over $20 million in
cars now, and it doesn't even matter.
I'd rather drive a Kia and be your age again.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Los Angeles is the number six city
in the entire world with the most millionaires.
Today, we're going to be going all
over the entire city asking these multimillionaires
how they created their wealth and how you can
start your path to becoming financially free in 2023.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
Finance.
So I'm in private equity.
And what was the turning
point like getting into that business?
Did you always know that
you were going to do that?
No, it was pretty scary.
I spent probably about six years
in isolation to break into investment banking.
Grew up homeless, first-generation college student.
Dad left when I was two.
At the turning point when I was 18, my
mom actually had some mental struggles and battles with suicide,
and I decided that I wanted to roll up
my sleeves and go play with the big boys.
And so I graduated from the number
one business school in the world, Wharton.
Now I'm in finance doing private equity,
and it's been a dream come true.
That's incredible, man.
Seriously.
So let me ask you this.
As someone who's in private equity, right, when it
comes to the way that people look at money,
what would you say is the number
one thing that separates the middle class
and those who end up
really acquiring and building that wealth?
Risk aversion.
If you look at the top Forbes list,
like the top 500, about 83% of that list,
they were willing to go to
negative $3 million before hitting it big.
And so the risk appetite to actually
kick it up to the next level,
I think is something that a lot of
people need to take into perspective when they say,
you know, I want to win.
What's been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Multiple millions, yeah.
What would you say is the best financial
advice that you ever received throughout your lifetime?
Bet big and lose early.
Don't worry about how much money you're making
on a single transaction or a single investment.
In your younger years, it's all about developing a playbook.
And so you got to be willing to
lose just as bad as you're willing to win.
When you take L's, it's
not about like the L itself.
It's like, how can I adjust my playbook
so I never have to take the L again?
You do that, you'll have a lot more wins.
Great interview, man.
You crushed that.
Seriously, man.
I appreciate you.
That has got to be one of
the most wholesome interviews that I've ever done.
He went from living in poverty and being homeless
to creating millions of dollars worth
of wealth in the private equity industry.
And I love what he said.
The most successful people are willing
to risk it all to be successful
and create millions of dollars in wealth.
That's the only way you're going
to be able to make it.
Shout out to him.
Gave a great interview.
And let's go get this next one.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
Well, I'm not going to tell
you the industry that I was in.
I'm just going to tell you that
in order to be successful in life,
especially in this country, opportunity.
When someone gives you the opportunity,
take it and run with it.
Nobody dies from hard work.
And nobody dies from working
16, 18 hours a day, seven.
When I was young, your age,
I wanted to have a Lamborghini.
And I thought that was going to
be the greatest thing, achievement I'll ever have.
I have over $20 million in cars now.
And it doesn't even matter.
I'd rather drive a Kia and be your age again.
Because now I can be the
president of the United States and beyond.
Young people like you, be grateful,
work hard, set your goals high.
Last thing I'm going to tell you, school is fantastic.
But it's only a tool.
It's not the ends to all.
However, you're going to study
anything, study finance and study law.
Not because of anything other
than if you understand numbers,
that is the universal language of the world.
Because you can just sit in your
office and figure everything out with just numbers.
Law, not to be a lawyer.
God forbid anybody be a lawyer or a doctor.
Don't be any of those things.
That's for ordinary people.
What types of businesses did you run?
Like, were you in real estate or like what?
Manufacturing.
But if I was to do
it again, I wouldn't do manufacturing.
It's a lot of work.
And a lot of responsibility.
And now I can only imagine if I was
your age and just knew what I was doing.
I was just telling my friend I
could be homeless today right here at 18.
And I could be the Jeff Bezos, Elon Musk
and Bill Gates combined and buy 15 Warren Buffetts.
Because the opportunity is there
for you to go after it.
It really is.
And it's that easy.
And people that think, oh my God, I'm not lucky.
I don't have this.
I wasn't given that.
Bullshit.
Thank you so much for your time.
I really appreciate that.
Have a great day, sir.
All right, you guys.
That was an absolutely insane.
That guy has companies that have generated
hundreds of millions of dollars in the manufacturing
industry.
We stopped him on the corner in Beverly Hills
to get a quick interview and ask him for his
advice for all the entrepreneurs out there.
Gave some great game.
But let's keep this LA video
rolling and go get this next one.
All right, you guys.
We are on Rodeo Drive in
Beverly Hills, Los Angeles at Peter Marco.
But we're about to interview Peter Marco.
He's the owner of this company.
This is a nine, nearly 10 figure business.
And he's worth hundreds of millions of dollars.
We're going to ask him the secret to creating
wealth as a business owner and one of the
most competitive cities in the entire world.
Let's see what he has to say.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career?
Topless dancing.
But I failed.
So I used to be a male dancer.
Then that didn't work.
So I figured I'd get involved in the jewelry business.
That's a joke, by the way.
How long have you been an entrepreneur for?
So I started in the jewelry business
when I was about 15 years old.
I'm 62 now.
So it's been a lifetime career, 47 years.
And at 15, you don't really
know what you want to be.
I grew up in New York.
And you kind of just go with the flow.
Things were like falling into place for me.
And I kind of rolled with it.
Where did the passion come from with jewelry?
So I am the first one in my family.
I came from a single family.
No father.
Since I was four years old, grew
up on the streets of New York.
And there was no direction or guidance.
I just got a break when I was 15
to clean bathrooms for a jewelry company in Manhattan.
And then they hired me to be a messenger boy.
And then I was promoted to a
jeweler and a setter and a polisher.
And then I traveled the whole
world for them for like 25 years.
I did Europe, Asia, Canada, Cayman Islands,
Caribbean, the whole United States with a
bag of jewelry worth $3 million.
And when you start making money and you're
a poor kid, that kind of motivates you and
drives you.
So I really didn't know what I wanted to do.
I wasn't college material.
I wasn't school material.
I couldn't wait to get out of high school.
I barely made it through it.
But then you give the guy
the football and he runs with it.
He doesn't look back.
And that's kind of what happened.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever generated in a single year for
your company?
I wouldn't disclose that.
Okay.
But I will tell you that, humbly speaking,
because this is Rodeo Drive in Beverly Hills,
there's many committees here because
of the tourism and everything.
They keep record of everything.
And back in 2017 or 18, they told me
they don't even use my figures because I was doing
more business than anyone in Beverly Hills.
More than 90% of businesses don't make it past 5%.
You've had a career in
entrepreneurship that's been nearly 40 years.
What is the greatest lesson that you've
learned that you pass on to someone else?
What's worked for me personally, I don't
care what your religion is, your culture is.
I don't care where you
are from anywhere in the world.
People want to deal with people who are real.
Keep it real.
Your word is the only
thing you have in this world.
All this could be gone tomorrow, but I would
make it back because of my honor, my values,
my morals.
So if you give your
word on something, you follow through.
You just keep your word and do clearly.
You're a clean business and people will flock
to you because everyone wants to deal with
winners.
Nobody wants to deal with
a shady guy or a loser.
Everybody wants to deal with the
best and work hard at it.
You know, there's a restaurant in the corner
that closes 10 or 11 o'clock at night.
For years and years, I was
the last one to leave the street.
I'd leave and the restaurant was closed.
What is that telling you?
I'm leaving 12, 1 o'clock in the morning.
What you put into it, you're
going to get out of it.
When you see that gymnast and you see
that gymnast doing five flips in the air, coming
down, they practice.
They live it.
They create it.
And I think what also helps
me is it's not a job.
It's a passion.
I love what I do.
And that makes the world of a difference.
If you're going to get up every morning and
regret where you got to go and what you got
to do, you're not going to be good at it.
You know, a guy told me one
time, he said, look at that massive ocean.
Look at the Pacific Ocean.
It's massive.
And now you're a little boat out in that
ocean and all that water out there can kill you,
but it doesn't.
It's only the water that you
let in that will take you down.
So you just don't let it in.
And if it does get in, get rid of it.
You've heard the expression.
It's like the boxer.
You know, what do you do with that towel?
You can wipe off the sweat and keep
going, or you can throw the towel in.
You wipe it off and you just keep going
and stay true to the people around you and stay
true to the people you do business with.
Amazing interview, man.
Seriously.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate that.
Man, Peter Marko dropped nothing but absolute heat.
One of the most successful business
owners in all of Beverly Hills.
Gave some great game for all the entrepreneurs out there.
One of my favorites I've ever done.
Shout out to Peter Marko.
Let's go get this next one.
Excuse me, sir.
Quick question for you, man.
What do you do for a living right now?
I've been an entrepreneur since I was 15.
Started my first business in my bedroom.
And from there, sold it.
A couple of years later, did okay with it.
And I started my metal business card dot com.
What's the most amount of money that one
of your business has generated in a single year?
Oh, over five million.
You've been an entrepreneur for over 20 years.
What's the number one lesson that you've learned
that you would pass on to someone who's starting
a business in 2023?
The sooner you can find great people
and delegate, the better off you'll be.
I think the fundamental is as an entrepreneur
starting a business, you want to do everything.
And in fact, you kind of have to
because you can't afford to hire good people.
But if you figure out that the good
people cost less than doing it yourself, you'll make
strides very quickly.
You brought up kind of building that team in, right?
What do you look for in a
business partner when you're assembling a company?
That's a great question.
There's a book by Patrick Lencioni, The Ideal
Team Player, and it goes over three things
humble, smart and driven.
If it's those three things, you're golden.
What is your best networking advice
for the younger generation out there?
How have you been able to build your
network, find those relationships in the business world?
Do you have a business card on you?
A business card?
Yeah, I think so.
Let me.
I got one, actually.
Here you go.
Okay.
So paper, as expected, it just doesn't stand out.
And I think what happens is most people
look at business cards as an office expense.
Pens.
They look at business cards, but really it's marketing.
You know, successful people are so busy and
they can take you places that money can't.
But to get in front of them and to be
remembered, there's not anything I can think of that has
the impact.
You can literally hand somebody a metal business
card and without saying a word, start an entire
conversation.
So final thing, your network literally is
your net worth, but you're never going to
make a network if you don't stand out.
So this is your business card.
That's the metal business card.
It's the actual metal.
Where can everybody find these?
So mymetalbusinesscard.com.
And if you use code HARDKNOX,
we're going to offer 20% off.
This is for anybody that wants
to stand out and leave a memory.
Ripple impression.
This Los Angeles video has been absolutely
insane, but the best is yet to come.
So stay tuned and be sure to like
and subscribe for amazing content on the way.
Let's get back to the interviews.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career?
I went into the entertainment industry,
full on agent, manager, TV show creator.
So for me, I'm a Jack of
all trades as an executive in the industry.
How did you know that you
wanted to go into the entertainment business?
Was that always something that you set out
to do when you were a kid or?
Well, growing up here in Beverly Hills, I
was blessed to have a lot of friends whose
families were in the business.
So.
I saw it all around me and I basically wanted
to follow in the footsteps of a lot of my
friends, parents who were really
famous and really well known.
And at 15 years old, I got a job at
Interscope that then turned into a job at UTA and turned
into a job of me
owning my own management production company.
And for me, I have
some precedent setting deals at networks.
I have some of the highest paid people
that have ever made the biggest network deals in
reality TV.
So the highest paid people on reality shows,
those are deals that my company has done.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Well, we're not going to say
that number, but it's in the millions.
A lot of people don't have a great idea.
They'll start that business.
They don't know how to scale and grow it.
What's the biggest thing?
Well, the most important thing is
that you have to know your value.
So if your idea is great, your product is great.
You have to have partners around you and
the distribution around you to be able to push
it out in the market so that
the money goes up and up and up.
And that's what we've been able to do.
Luckily for me working in media, there's
so many networks, so many streamers, so many
places to sell to now that you have
a lot more opportunity to sell your product.
You crushed that, man.
Seriously, man.
It was absolutely crazy running into David.
That is a media mogul.
He's closed some of the biggest deals and
been the architect behind some of the biggest
deals in all of Hollywood entertainment history.
It makes sense why we ran into him
out in Beverly Hills and Los Angeles, the entertainment
capital of the world.
But let's keep this video rolling.
Go get the next one.
Excuse me, sir.
Quick question for you, man.
Is this your Lamborghini?
Yeah, it is.
What do you do for a living, man?
How are you able to afford
a Lamborghini out in Los Angeles?
I own a law firm in Los Angeles.
You own a law firm.
How long have you been a business owner for?
Coming on seven years.
What's been the most amount of money
that you've ever generated in a single year?
I think that's attorney client
privilege, but several millions of dollars.
Several millions of dollars.
And we go all over the country
asking business owners their advice to young entrepreneurs.
Could we ask you a few questions for the channel?
Absolutely.
Awesome.
Let's run it.
Did you go to college?
I went to UCLA.
Do you think a college degree is
necessary to be successful in today's society?
I think so.
I think you should never
go cheap on your own education.
What would you say is the best
financial advice that you've ever received throughout your
lifetime?
A dollar spent on yourself is a dollar never wasted.
Are you a reader by any chance?
I do like to read.
Do you like to read?
What's the number one book recommendation
that you have for someone out there?
I would say, Netflix.
I've never split the difference by Chris Voss.
By asking the right questions and communicating properly,
you'll be able to get what you want
in a deal.
You have a Lamborghini out in Los Angeles.
For someone who's watching this, what would you
say is the best advice that you would
tell the younger generation today?
I would tell them to start a business
and right when you start getting some profits,
put that right back into advertising and marketing.
Brand yourself.
Single-handedly, I think branding
is the most important thing.
That's your identity and your trademark to the public.
You could be the best lawyer.
You could be the best doctor.
You can best real estate agent.
But unless there's people knocking on your
door, unless people know who you are, you're
not going to ever be known in this world.
So the number one thing
is branding, advertising, and marketing.
My God, you crushed that.
Seriously, bro.
Los Angeles was an absolute movie, everyone.
It was crazy to make this video, but I
want you to like and subscribe for amazing content
coming soon.
And click here to watch us going
all over Miami asking multimillionaire supercar owners
how they became wealthy.